[{"answer": "We were blindsided by everything that has happened past week and a half.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 35, "question": "How do you feel?", "qSentId": 34}, {"answer": "We officially had heard some -- just a little gossip around town, some community, you know, gossip, as every community has.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 37, "question": "I mean, what rumors had you heard prior to this week?", "qSentId": 36}, {"answer": "I'm not for sure.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 41, "question": "Why do you think that was?", "qSentId": 40}, {"answer": "That was this summer, this past summer, 2011, the golf tournament raise -- the fund-raiser that they have.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "And when did that happen?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "I'm not at liberty to say.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "Who was that, from the Second Mile charity?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "I believe, according to the media and according to the grand jury, it says that in 2008, the Second Mile put him, you know, he stepped down and he was not allowed to be involved in the activities with children.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "Do you now believe that at the time you were told there was nothing to worry about that actually they knew that the charity was well aware of what was going on?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "We are hoping to -- in the community to recover, we are hoping to find someone that will step up and be a leader and, you know, help our community.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 62, "question": "What would you do about this, if anything?", "qSentId": 61}, {"answer": "We're looking for someone in our community to step up and be a leader.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "What would you describe the current mood of the students as?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "Well, I think the prosecutor's office is definitely looking at all of the evidence.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "From a legal perspective, I would imagine that's a dangerous position to be adopted right now, isn't it?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "Are you a pedophile?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "Am I sexually to underage boys?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "RIEL: Well, I'll say this, that it's highly unusual for a defense attorney to let his client be interviewed in that fashion, and for exactly the reason we just saw.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "How ill-advised was that interview, do you think?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "Well, I think that our system is innocent until proven.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "Is that -- is that unhelpful to the legal process, having him convicted in the court of popular opinion?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": "Well, I think -- I'm not really prepared to discuss whether I think he was involved in a cover-up.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "What is your view of had his legal position here, in terms of potentially being involved in a cover-up from all that you've seen and read and heard?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "Well, as we mentioned before, the fact that it took him a while to answer that one question, the way he meandered around some other questions, his referring to horsing around and things like that -- it didn't strike me as a very good defensive posture -- let's put it that way, coming from a lawyer.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "And from all of your experience in these kind of cases, when you heard Jerry Sandusky talking, what did your gut feel tell you about the kind of language that he was using and his behavioral pattern?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "While this kind of allegation is quite interesting from a person who is from a country that already possess nuclear weapons and is a renegade country in the eye of NPT.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "What is your reaction to that?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "Well, the cameras of IAEA are 24 hours working over there.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 186, "question": "If as you say, it's all completely peaceful and above- board, why don't you just let everybody come have a look and inspect them in the peace and tranquility that you talk of?", "qSentId": 185}, {"answer": "Holocaust is a historical matter.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 202, "question": "Do you believe in it?", "qSentId": 201}, {"answer": "Do you feel threatened in Iran in the sense that most world leaders now are being openly hostile towards Iran, whether it's President Sarkozy, President Obama, President Medvedev -- I mean, everyone is cueing up to say you are a dangerous country.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "Our view is that, why not like centuries Muslims, Christians and Jews could live together in such beautiful piece of land which is called Palestine?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "Well, there are two reasons.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "So, the kind of obvious question to me, is if you're not developing nuclear weapons, which you are saying other countries have, Israel to Pakistan and certainly America, many other countries have nuclear weapons, why wouldn't Iran want to have a nuclear weapon to defend itself?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, before assessing these claims on the military and defense and security basis, I think this is a good distraction from the basic problems in the United States.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "How do you view military action against you?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "Total and complete nonsense, Piers.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "What was your reaction?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "Well, I think that's exactly what's going on.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "What is the right way to deal with Iran, if they're going to flagrantly ignore any form of international community opinion on this?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "Well, we're still in the preseason, Piers.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 298, "question": "Are you frustrated that you are still lagging in the polls when the credentials that you seem to offer at this very challenging time for America, particularly on the international stage, seem so much more impressive than many of your rivals?", "qSentId": 297}, {"answer": "He has name recognition.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "As things stand, he's going to walk it, isn't he?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "Watch it, dad.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "Are they a force for good or catastrophe in your campaign?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "Well, he hasn't had a chance to have America see him yet.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "And what can he do about it?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "Careful.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "What is the secret Jon Huntsman like?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "Is he boring?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "New Hampshire loves an underdog.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "What is the one thing that is going to drive you past Mitt Romney?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "I -- it wouldn't be for me to comment.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "Do you disagree?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "We think our dad had the best haircut.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "But who had the worst haircut, in your opinion?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "Piers, I don't have a choice.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "Jon, do you worry that your daughters are going to land you -- you're going to wake up one morning and all hell has broken loose on Twitter?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "IVINGSTON: Look, we're really doing this for a very serious reason.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "Or is it just whatever goes through your minds?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "I guess you'll just have to wait and see.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "Have you got any more shocking surprises for us?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "111116pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "What are you worth?", "qSentId": 524}]